

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Game Design
Narrative Design
Project Management
Live Ops Design
Game Analysis
Unity Engine
VR/AR Development
C#
Python

LANGUAGES

Farsi (Native) Turkish (Native) English (Professional, IELTS Band 8)

CONTACT



+98 9368251081



vahidranandeh@gmail.com



https://www.vonbird.com/

SOCIAL

Linkedin: Vahid Ranandeh

Skype: @von_bird

VAHID RANANDEH

GAME DESIGNER, WRITER

ABOUT

I'm a Game Designer and Writer, with 5 years of experience in game design and 10 years of experience in writing. I'm passionate about both creating and playing video games, and I like to face new challenges in bringing fresh ideas to life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIRECTOR, GAME DESIGNER, WRITER VOIDI 2015 - Present

- Developed a game called "Pursuit of Redemption" for PC
- Led a team of 6 Game Developers
- Wrote Scripts for cutscenes, in-game dialogues, and collectibles
- Designed over 50 puzzle, platformer, and top-down levels

GAME DEVELOPER

Legends of Learning | 2019 - Present

- Developed 5 WebGL math learning games with Unity
- Received overwhelmingly positive reviews by teachers and students
- Satisfied the learning objectives given by Legends of Learning
- Used Jira for Scrum
- Collaborated with the team members using Miro
- The games are published on Legend of Learning's website and played by thousands of students

VR DEVELOPER

University of Tabriz | 2018 - 2020

- Developed a VR Game Development Platform using Unity Engine
- Worked with SteamVR plugin
- Published the results of my work as my Master's Thesis
- $\bullet\,$ Developed a project using the platform for "National Elite's Foundation", as the project manager of a team of 10
- The Platform is currently being used by the University's students to develop VR games and apps

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER ENGINEERING

University of Tabriz | 2014 - 2018

- Rank 1 of Class
- GPA: 18.32 / 20 (4.6 / 5)
- Held University's 1st & 2nd annual Game Development Workshops
- Developed a mobile app called "Teeleh" to buy, sell, and trade video games
- Worked at University's Innovation Center

MASTER OF SCIENCE, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

University of Tabriz | 2018 - 2020

- Rank 1 of Class
- GPA: 19.05 / 20 (4.8 / 5)
- Founder of University's Game Lab
- Lecturer and Tutor at VR Development Conference